<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Publications on Home</title>
    <link>/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Publications on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MASTER THESIS - Learning Shapes for Efficient Segmentation of 3D Medical Images using Point Cloud</title>
      <link>/publications/masterthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/masterthesis/</guid>
      <description>Abstract In this report, we present a novel approach for 3D medical image segmentation using point clouds. 3D Convolutional Neural Networks have been the most dominating networks in medical image processing but they require large memory footprints and training samples. Hence we used point clouds to represent the image instead of voxels. Point clouds are lightweight and contain shape and smoother surface information. We extracted the point clouds from 3D voxel images using canny edge detection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PREPRINT - Vignette detection and reconstruction of composed ornaments with a strengthened autoencoder</title>
      <link>/publications/dae/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/dae/</guid>
      <description>Abstract A strengthened autoencoder formed by placing an object detector upstream of a decoder is here developed in the context of the model-helped human analysis of composed ornaments from a dictionary of vignettes. The detection part is in charge to detect regions of interest containing some vignette features, and the decoding part to ensure vignette reconstruction with a relative quality depending on feature match. Images of ornaments without typographical composition are generated in order to properly assess the performance of each of the two parts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
